Guide to the Birge M. Clark Architectural Drawings SC0838
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Architectural Drawings
  - Fisher Research Laboratories; Fisher Research Laboratories One-Story Shop Addition, 1943-03-08; 584 (Box Sc2)
    9 drawings
    Address: 1961 University Ave.
  - Stern, Ruth Lucie; Nurses’ Cottage for the Palo Alto Hospital, 1940-02-12; 510 (Box Sb9)
    9 plans, 1940; See also Job #679
  - Stern, Ruth Lucie; Nurses’ Cottage at Palo Alto Hospital Addition, 1948-11-09; 679 (Box Sc3)
    9 plans, 1948; See also Job #510
    City: Palo Alto (Stanford ?)
  - Boy Scouts of America; Sea Scout Base for Stanford Area Council of the Boy Scouts of America, at Yacht Harbor, 531
    Date of Contract: Oct. 18, 1940; Jan. 2001 no drawings found
    Address: Yacht Harbor
  - Stanford University; Stanford War Memorial, 45
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Addison Ave. School, 221
    Date of Contract: June 25, 1924
    Address: Addison Ave.
    Category: schools
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Cubberley High School
    Address: Middlefield Rd.
  - Santa Clara County; Barron Park Elementary School, 1947-10-23; 641
    Feb. 2000 no dwgs found
    Address: Barron and El Centro Aves.
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Board of Education Channing Addition, 1932-08-19; 362
    Administration building, 1 plan, 1932
    Address: 543 Channing St.
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Channing Gym, 1933-12-27; 376 (Box Sc4)
    3 plans, 1933
    Address: Channing & Webster
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Palo Alto Union High School, 28
    Original Plans by Allison & Allison
    Address: Churchill Ave.
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Palo Alto Union High School Addition #1, 1923-09; 182 (Box Sd8)
    8 sheets + 3 blue prints = Roll 1; 12 sheets on vellum = Roll 2
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Palo Alto Union High School Addition #2, 278
    Date of Contract: April 5, 1927
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Palo Alto Union High School Boys Gymnasium Addition #3, 1928; 314 (Box Sc7)
    12 drawings, 1928
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Palo Alto High School Earthquake Reconstruction, 386
    Date of Contract: Aug. 22, 1934
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Palo Alto Union High School Cafeteria-Kitchen Public Works Administration Project, 1935; 403 (Box Sc4)
    4 plans - pencil on tissue, 1935
    Architect: Birge M. and David B. Clark
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Palo Alto Union High School Cafeteria-Kitchen Public Works Administration Project, 1935; 405 (Box Sc4)
    1 plan incorrectly numbered as file 404 - pencil on tissue, 1935; ROLLED WITH FILE NUMBER 403
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Palo Alto Union High School Industrial Shop Building, 599
    Date of Contract: Oct. 26, 1945; Jan. 2001 no drawings found
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Palo Alto Senior High School, 646 (Box Sc6)
    baseball bleacher plan, 1947 - pencil on paper [#1 of 2, #2 missing]
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Crescent Park Elementary School, 1947-10-23; 642
    Address: Dana St.
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Crescent Park Elementary School Seven Classroom Addition and Lavatory Facilities, 688
    Date of Contract: May 16, 1949
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Walter Hays School Seven Classrooms, Teachers Room, Boys and Girls Lavatories, 1946-08-27; 625
    Feb. 2000 dwgs not found
    Address: Middlefield Road
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Walter Hays School Addition, 202
    Date of Contract: May 17, 1924
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; David Starr Jordan, Jr. High School, 432
    Date of Contract: Nov. 18, 1936
  - Castilleja School, 1928-07-06; 311 (Box Sc7)
    Classroom, 7 drawings, 1928
  - Castilleja School Chapel, 1926-03-11; 256 (Box Sd9)
  - Castilleja School Gymnasium, 1929-07-01; 333 (Box Sc9)
    9 drawings, 1929
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; South Palo Alto School, 258
    Date of Contract: April 20, 1926
    Address: 2700 Middlefield Road
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; South Palo Alto School, 398
    Date of Contract: Sept. 1935
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; South Palo Alto Schools Two Classroom Addition, 530
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; South Palo Alto School Addition: Five Classrooms, Administrative Unit, and Lobby, 1946-04-23; 618
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Palo Alto Union High School Boys Gymnasium Addition, 1946-05-24; 624
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; South Palo Alto School Nine Classroom Addition plus Teachers' Room, Library, Nurse's Room, 678
    Date of Contract: Nov. 8, 1948
  - Board of Education, Palo Alto Schools; Elizabeth Van Auken Elementary School
    Date of Contract: Sept. 21, 1949
  - Registrar’s Office; Stanford University Registrar’s Office: New Partition, Counter, Screen, and Relocated Glass Partitions
    Date of Contract: August 1942
  - Allen, Mrs. C.G.; Stanford University Men’s Rest Home, 508 (Box Sb9)
  - Dining Hall; Stanford University Dining Hall, 585
  - Palo Alto Military Academy Small Building on Grounds, 277 (Box Sd9)
    Not Supervised; 2 sheets
  - Hoover, Herbert, 29 (Box Sc12)
    26 blueprints - not marked with any file number, 1919 and undated
    Address: Gerona
  - Blake, Thomas B., 1923-01-18; 171 (Box Sd8)
    4 sheets
    Address: Addison Ave & Waverley Street
  - Snedden, David, 1947-08-25; 650 (Box Sc6)
    5 plans, 1947 - pencil on paper
    Address: 440 Amherst St.
  - Snedden, David, 1935-10-18; 404 (Box Sc4)
    3 plans - pencil on paper
    Address: 460 Amherst St.
  - Finch, Nathan [Snedden, David], 1948; 404 (Box Sc4)
    File # 669 (ref. 404) "Alteration to David Snedden Residence" - 1 item 1948; Unnumbered - elevation for dining room detail, 1950 [Stromquist]
  - Staub, H. H., 1941-06-24; 546 (Box Sc2)
    8 plans, 1941
    Address: 481 Amherst Street
  - Lee, Mrs. Russell V. A., 1937-08-18; 454 (Box Sc5)
    Address: 615, 625 Amherst Street
  - Pease, Howard, 421 (Box Sc5)
    5 plans, 1936
    Address: Bryant & Palo Alto Streets - not built
  - Drysdale, G. S., 1935-11-25; 407 (Box Sc4)
    5 plans, 1935
    Address: 1991 Bryant St.
  - Clark, Don F., 1924-08-11; 211 (Box Sc10)
    Address: Byron Street (betw. Kellogg and Embarcadero)
  - Clark, Birge M., 1922-02-11; 151 (Box Sc1)
    4 sheets (need restoration)
    Address: Embarcadero & Webster
  - Laumeister, Gustav, 1923-05-08; 180 (Box Sd8)
    4 drawings, 1923
    Address: 544 Coleridge Ave.
  - Niebel, Mrs. Celia E., 361 (Box Sc4)
    3 plans, 1932
    Address: 1480 Byron St.
  - Howe, Avery J., 1931-10-13; 357 (Box Sc4)
    Plans, 1931
    Address: 524 Center Street
  - Kirk, Dr. Josiah H., 1925-08-05; 243 (Box Sd9)
    Address: 232 Coleridge Ave.
  - Peet, Mrs. Harriet M., 174
    Address: 420 Coleridge Ave.
  - Dunker, Mr & Mrs. John A.; Kunker Estate Co., 1926-06-12; 269 (Box Sd9)
    11 Sheets - Elevation, Plan, heating Plan, Details, Plot Plan.; 1 Sheet - topography sketch,; 1 Sheet - Site Plan in 1981 with Clark, Staromquist & Sandstorm
    Address: 420 Maple Street
  - Kinney, Miss Ettie, 315 (Box Sc7)
    2 drawings, 1928. Rolled with File #283
    Address: 455 Coleridge Ave.
  - Hays, E. G., 1921-06-01; 35 (Box Sc1)
    3 Sheets
    Address: Cooper Street
  - Cobbe, Janet, 1922-09-05; 162 (Box Sd8)
    3 sheets + 1 sheet
    Address: Cowper St. & Addison Ave.
  - Murphy, Bessie & Jennie, 651 (Box Sc6)
    Alterations & addition, 4 plans, 1947; 3 plans by A. B. Clark for residence of Edmund W. Brown, n.d. - ink on linen [original bldg at 412 ?]
    Address: 412 Cowper Street
  - Lansdale, Philip M., 1925-10-14; 250 (Box Sd9)
    3 sheets
    Address: 657 Cowper St.
  - D'Audney, C. R., 1935-05-17; 393 (Box Sc4)
    Cottage, 6 plans, 1935
    Address: 1928 Cowper St.
  - Stern, Lucie, 1942-01-02; 561 (Box Sc2)
    2 drawings, 12/24/41
    Address: 1950 Cowper St. - garden house
  - Stern, Mrs. Louis, 1932-02-08; 360 (Box Sc11)
    Two residences for Mrs. Louis Stern, on the South side of Cowper Street. 4 sheets, tissue, Jan. 27, 1932 - numbers 4, 8, 9, and one where the number is illegible
    Address: 1950, 1990 Cowper St.
  - Hutton, Samuel R., 1925-01-23; 224 (Box Sc10)
    3 drawings
    Address: 1966 Cowper St.
  - Ames, Mrs. Rhoda H., 1936-04-14; 418 (Box Sc11)
    6 plans, 1936; 1 plan, 1937
    Address: 2250 Cowper St.
  - Whitehead, Jesse, 1926-11-22; 268 (Box Sd9)
    10 sheets
    Address: 51 Crescent Drive
  - Eells, Walter C., 1928-03-20; 298 (Box Sc7)
    10 drawings, 1928
    Address: 735 Dolores St.
  - Field, Andrew J., 1930-07-16; 350
    Address: 557 East Crescent Drive
  - Speidel, Merritt C., 1938-10-06; 479 (Box Sc8)
    9 plans, 1938; 1 plat map by city surveyer, Sept. 1938
    Address: 101 Edgewood Drive
  - Speidel, Merritt C., 1941-05-26; 543 (Box Sc8)
    1 plan, 1941; ROLLED WITH FILE #479
    Address: 101 Edgewood Drive - porch addition
  - Quinby, J. A., 1947-08-19; 640
    9 plans, 1947 - pencil on paper
    Address: 120 Edgewood Drive
  - Roth, A. W., 634 (Box Sc6)
    2 plans for living quarters over garage, 1946 - pencil on tissue
    Address: 149 Edgewood Dr.
  - Saier, Dr. & Mrs. Milton, 1939-10-24; 505
    sleeping porch addition
    Address: 1474 Edgewood Drive
  - Saier, Milton, 1935-11-09; 406 (Box Sc11)
    5 plans - pencil on tissue
  - Mudgett, Wm. A., 1936-05-22; 424 (Box Sc5)
    6 plans, 1936
    Address: 180 Edgewood Dr.
  - Blackburn, J. M., 1926-02-01; 253 (Box Sd9)
    Address: 570, 596 Coleridge Ave.
  - Fox, Mrs. Herbert, 1935-07-09; 394 (Box Sc4)
    13 plans, 1935
    Address: 526 Coleridge Ave.
  - Brooke, Mrs. Philip, 489 (Box Sc8)
    5 plans for various additions, 1936-39; [SEE ALSO JOB #394]
  - Morse, Mr. & Mrs. Lester L., 1929; 330 (Box Sc9)
    Approx. 17 drawings, 1929
  - Morell, George F., 1928-06-18
    note: incorrect file number (11/30/00)
    Address: Coleridge Ave & Cowper St.
  - Gurley, Lee S., 1933-08-01; 373 (Box Sc4)
    7 plans, 1933
    Address: 100 Edgewood Drive
  - Clark, Birge M., 1936-11-23; 435 (Box Sc5)
    Address: 190 Edgewood Drive
  - Atwater, Ray, 1948-04-27; 668 (Box Sc3)
    Address: 155 Edgewood Drive
  - Langnecker, H. L., 37 (Box Sc1)
    1 Sheet
    Address: 320 Embarcadero Rd.
  - Price, Frances (Mrs. Webster Street), 1924-11-17; 218
    Address: 590 Embarcadero Rd.
  - Jacobson, Mrs. Emily, 1924-08-18; 214 (Box Sc10)
  - Marx, Guido V.D., 1934-05-22; 383
    addition to residence - one bedroom and bath
    Address: 1935 Emerson St.
  - Newsom, A. P., 1923-04-23; 179 (Box Sd8)
    2 sheets, cottage for Mrs. Adelaide P. Newsom, March 29, 1923; 1 sheet, garage for Mr. Branner K. Newsom, Oct. 23, 1923; [same address for both]
    Address: Fulton & Everett Streets
  - Salz, C. F., 1936-05-11; 422 (Box Sc5)
    Address: 1766 Fulton Street
  - Hardy, Judge Edward E., 1935-09-23; 401 (Box Sc4)
    Address: 1830 Fulton St.
  - Hardy, Judge Edward E., 1948-10-22; 680 (Box Sc4)
    3 plans, 1968; ROLLED WITH FILE NO. 401
  - Field, A. J., 197 (Box Sd8)
    Address: 619 Guinda
  - Waterhouse, S. W., 1936-04-17; 420 (Box Sc5)
    4 plans, 1936
    Address: 407 Hale St.
  - Whitling, T., 238
    Address: Hanilton Ave. & Guinda
  - Koontz, Mr. & Mrs. John A., 1929-01-22; 324
    Address: 955 Hamilton
  - Koontz, John A., 1925-06-02; 235 (Box Sc10)
    6 drawings, includes 1 from 1929 remodel
  - Wilson, Walter V., 1932-09-12; 363 (Box Sc4)
    4 plans, 1932, and 1 plan, 1938
    Address: 1120 Hamilton Ave.
  - Wilson, Walter V., 1939-03; 487
  - Hapgood, Frank A., 1938-10-29; 481 (Box Sc8)
    6 plans, 1938
    Address: 1220 Hamilton Ave.
  - Marx, Guido V. D., 1937-07-07; 452 (Box Sc11)
    Address: 1491 Hamilton Ave.
  - Saldierina, Mrs. Anna, 1926-02-04; 254 (Box Sd9)
    Address: 561 Homer Ave.
  - Ormsby, Herbert, 1933-03-28; 368 (Box Sc4)
    4 plans, 1933
    Address: 155 Island Drive
  - Masters, Alfred R., 1935-05-20; 392 (Box Sc4)
    6 plans, 1935
    Address: 111 Island Drive
  - Reynolds, Dr. Harry B., 1926-10; 275 (Box Sd9)
    Address: 360 Kellogg
  - Reynolds, Dr. Harry B., 1928-03-09; 296 (Box Sc7)
    Address: 360 Kellogg Ave.
  - Marx, C. D. estate, 1940-02-29; 513 (Box Sb9)
    "group of ten residences, 325-375 Kingsley" - plans, 1940
    Address: 325 - 375 Kingsley Ave.
  - Hare, Brewer & Kelley, 1939-02; 488 (Box Sc8)
    "Exposition model homes tours display home, Leland Manor"; 9 plans, 1939
    Address: Leland Manor
  - Kelley, Wm. M., 494
    4 plans, 1939
  - Roberts, W.A., 1923-03; 179 (Box Sd8)
    3 Sheets, April 12, 1923
    Address: Lowell Avenue (betw. Webster and Cowper)
  - Crandall, Berton W., 1920-07-17; 32 (Box Sc1)
    Address: 335 Lowell Avenue, Lot 12 & 14, Block 19
  - Van Wyck, M., 1928-03-06; 297 (Box Sc7)
    9 drawings, 1928
    Address: 465 Lowelll Ave. - guest house
  - Lovell, B. C. and E. B., 1923-12-26; 194 (Box Sd8)
    4 Sheets
    Address: 555 Lowell Avenue
  - Richards, I. S., 1921; 36 (Box Sc1)
    Address: 563 Lowell Avenue, Lot 8 & 9 Block 30
  - Goodenough, Wells P., 445 (Box Sc5)
    4 plans, 1937; 1 plan 1943 for fireplace; [two index cards, one is missing a file number; file #445 is marked "not done"]
    Address: 569 Lowell Ave.
  - Palo Alto Land Co., 1923-08; 187 (Box Sd8)
    Address: Maple Street & Crescent Park
  - Nichols, W. Edwin, 1928-10-29; 319
    Plans by Leslie I. Nichols.; card marked "3-31-38 tracings destroyed"
    Address: Maple Street
  - Pentler, S. J., 1938-07-01; 474 (Box Sc8)
    9 plans, 1938
    Address: 160 Martin Avenue
  - Kinney, Ettie, 1927-08-08; 283 (Box Sc7)
    11 drawings, 1927. Rolled with File #315
    Address: 455 Coleridge Avenue
  - Small, O. D., 1941; 553 (Box Sc2)
    2 drawings, Aug. 16, 1941
    Address: Menalto Ave. - not built
    City: North Palo Alto [Menlo Park]
  - Merner, Mrs. D. W., 1924-05-16; 203 (Box Sc10)
    five houses; 19 Sheets
    Address: 37 - 41 Middlefield Rd.
  - Quinby, J. H., 1922-09-23; 165 (Box Sd8)
    2 sheets + 1 revision sheet
    Address: 640 Middlefield Rd.
  - Allen, Lloyd, 1924-05-24; 204 (Box Sc10)
    3 drawings 5/5/1924
    Address: 1023 Middlefield Rd.
  - Jenkins, E. C., 1938-08-26; 478 (Box Sc8)
    Address: 425 Nevada St.
  - Patten, Mrs. Lenore Grey, 1941-11-21; 557 (Box Sc11)
    5 drawings, 1941; 1 drawing, 10/19/45; 1 drawing 5/10/43
    Address: 651 Newell Drive
  - Costello, Lorenz, 657
    8 plans, 194? - pencil on paper
    Address: Newell Road
  - Fette, Franklin C.; Grimes, Bruce D., 1941-06-26; 547 (Box Sc2)
    11 plans, 1941 and 1946; [name on 1946 plans is Bruce D. Grimes]
    Address: 60 Northampton Drive (Leland Manor)
  - Dunn, Dr. and Mrs. Robert T., 1940-08-21; 522 (Box Sb9)
    17 plans, 1940, plus one drawing for a Christmas card using house plan as part of the card, 1940
    Address: Page Mill Rd.
  - Dunn, Robert, 1942-04-15; 570
    Address: Page Mill Rd. - barn
  - Stromquist, Walter, 684
    Address: Palo Alto Ave.
  - Murphy, Miss Jennie H., 1926-09-16; 273 (Box Sd9)
    1 sheet
    Address: Ramona & University Ave. - addition
  - Clothes Closet, 631 (Box Sc6)
    1 plan of alterations, 1946 - pencil on tissue
    Address: 520 Ramona St.
  - Schink, C. E., 1936-04-04; 416 (Box Sc5)
    7 drawings, 1936
    Address: 300 Santa Rita Ave.
  - Schink, C. E., 1940-07; 515 (Box Sc5)
    4 drawings [ROLLED WITH FILE NO. 416]
    Address: 300 Santa Rita Ave. - addition
  - White, Mr. & Mrs. Frank G., 1931; 356 (Box Sc4)
    8 drawings
    Address: 330 Santa Rita Ave. - not built
  - Winterburn, J. C., 1940; 512 (Box Sb9)
    Group of four residences: 6 plans, 1940
    Address: Seale Ave. & Bryant St.
  - Lovell, Edith B., 1927-06-15; 282 (Box Sc7)
    4 drawings, 1927
    Address: 559 Seale Ave. [Lot #10, Block 32]
  - King, Mrs. Annie H., 1923-05-05; 181 (Box Sd8)
    Address: Seneca St. (between Forest & Hamilton)
  - Dnotes, John (plans completed), 1946-01-10; 615 (Box Sc6)
    5 plans, 1946 - pencil on tissue; 5 plans, 1946 - blueprints [accn 2006-322 - in process in GW403]; [residence was never built]
    Address: 275 Southampton Drive
  - King, Mrs. Annie H., 1924-08-12; 212 (Box Sc10)
  - Harvey, Mrs. Marguerite G., 1941-06-03; 542 (Box Sc2)
    3 plans, 1941
    Address: 477 Southampton Drive
  - Snell, Joel A., 1925-01-07; 223 (Box Sc10)
    Address: 1333 Tasso Street
  - Culver, G. B., 1924-06-30; 209 (Box Sc10)
    Address: Mirada & San Juan Hill - not built
  - Hunt, Harry J., 1941-04-21; 539 (Box Sb9)
    4 plans, 1941
    Address: 1941 Tasso St.
  - Sullivan, J. T., 1925-04-18; 232 (Box Sc10)
    4 Drawings
    Address: 427 Tennyson Ave.
  - Ellis, Gertrude M., 1928-07-12; 310 (Box Sc7)
    13 drawings, 1928
    Address: 595 Tennyson
  - Goodenough, Wells P., 441 (Box Sc5)
    7 plans, 1937; [plans are for Wells P. Goodenough; index card gives name as Paul Merner]
    Address: 701 Tennyson Ave.
  - Hink, O. K., 1939-05-11; 493 (Box Sc11)
    7 plans, 1939
    Address: 1150 University Avenue
  - Hapgood, Frank, 1933-05-15; 370 (Box Sc4)
    8 plans, 1933
    Address: 1570 University Ave.
  - Browne, A. A., 1945-02-26; 604 (Box Sc2)
    Five drawings, 2/20/45
    Address: 1755 University Ave.
  - Browne, A. A., 652 (Box Sc2)
    Shop, Lath house and Greenhouse: 1 Drawing, 7/21/47; ROLLED WITH #604
    Address: 1755 University Ave - addition
  - Horabin, W. C., 199
  - Wright, 173
    Address: Waverly Street
  - Hoover, Mrs. Margaret C., 1940-08-26; 527 (Box Sb9)
    2 plans, 1940
    Address: 2121 Waverley St.
  - Hoover, Mrs. Margaret C., 1941-05-12; 540 (Box Sb9)
    4 plans, 1941; 1 plan (File #540A), 1942
  - Palo Alto Building & Loan Association, 1922-09-20; 172 (Box Sd8)
    2 sheets - need restoration
    Address: Webster St. & Hawthorne Ave.
  - Vandervoort, H. M., 1926-08-11; 272 (Box Sd9)
    Address: Webster & Seale - not built
  - Holman, 1921-05-12; 38 (Box Sc1)
    Address: Webster St. near Embarcadero
  - Post, Henry. B., 1922-10-06; 166 (Box Sd8)
    Address: 1230 Webster St.
  - Marx, G. V. D., undated (Box Sd10)
    7 blueprints; [specifications for this house are in Box B1]
    Address: unknown
  - City of Palo Alto; Community Center
    Revision of Recreation Room Trusses, PA Community Center - 1934
  - Haynes, G. B., undated; 636 (Box Sc6)
    11 plans - pencil on paper
    Address: 760 Chiltern Road
    City: Hillsborough, CA
  - Fairley, William, 1947-1948; 660 (Box Sc3)
    8 plans - pencil on paper
    City: Atherton Heights
  - Marshall, F. N., 690 (Box Sc3)
    Kitchen alteration, 1949 - 1 item, pencil on paper
  - Dungan, T. A., 687 (Box Sc3)
    Floor plan and elevation - 2 items, pencil on papers, 1948
    City: Los Altos
  - Small, Boris, 692 (Box Sc3)
    3 items, 1944, ‘45, ‘49 - pencil on paper
    Address: 415 University Ave
  - College Park Elementary School, 686
    Cafetorium - 11 items (plans, elev., details, utils), pencil on paper, 1949
    Address: Coleman St.
    City: San Jose, CA
  - Chadwick, Joseph H.; Chadwick Seaside School - residence of Joseph Chadwick, 455 (Box Sc8)
    6 items (plans, elev, details), 1937 - pencil on tissue
    City: Rancho Palos Verdes, CA
  - Chadwick, Joseph H.; Chadwick Seaside School, 1937; 455 (Box Sc8)
    Roll 1: Aug. 9, 1937 dwgs (9) - plot plan, classroom & dorm units; Roll 2: Aug. 9, 1937 series of 17 plans; Roll 3: Misc. drawings, 1937
  - Golden Gate Internatl Exposition; Manilla Bureau of Public Works (Philippines) (Box Sd10)
    Proposed Philippines Exposition Building at the Golden Gate International Exposition for 1939 - 1938 drawings by architects of the Manilla Bureau of Public Works; see also File # 497
    City: San Francisco, CA
  - Children’s Hospital (Box Sd10)
    Perspectives for unspecified children’s hospital - pencil on tissue
  - H. M. Gousha Co., 1946; 619
    Address: Alameda & Davis
  - Benjamin Cory Elementary School, 1954; 710
    Includes projects 710 and 710A
  - Wideman & Son, Inc. Store Building, 762 (Box Sd10)
    2 drawings for mezzanine addition, 1953
  - LeRoy, Rene, 429 (Box Sc5)
    1 drawing for alteration and addition to residence, 1936
    City: Atherton, CA
  - unknown, 410 (Box Sc5)
    6 plans, 1935 - pencil on tissue
    Address: 425 West Santa Inez
  - James Graham Mfg. Company, 415 (Box Sc5)
    2 plans re addition, 1926
    City: Newark, CA
  - James Graham Mfg. Company, 549 (Box Sc5)
    1 plan re storage shed, 1941 [ROLLED WITH FILE 415]
  - Miles, Ferris W.; West Bay Motors, 610 (Box Sc2)
    3 plans for an addition, 1945; 1 drawing re radiant heating coils, 1946
    Address: Heller & Cassia Sts.
    City: Redwood City, CA
  - Fairley, William, 612 (Box Sc2)
    4 plans for guest house, 1945 - pencil on tissue
  - Ames, Dr. Richard, 462 (Box Sc8)
    Office building - 3 plans, 1937
    Address: Middlefield & Jefferson
  - Ames, Dr. Richard, 613 (Box Sc8)
    Addition to office building - 3 plans, 1945 [ROLLED WITH FILE 462]
  - Children’s Hospital, 621 (Box Sc6)
    Remodeling C. D. D. Building - 4 plans, 1946 - pencil on paper
  - Bettini, D., 626 (Box Sc6)
    Store building, 3 plans, 1946 - pencil on paper
    Address: 851, 853 El Camino Real
    City: Menlo Park, CA
  - Moreland Elementary School, 628 (Box Sc6)
    Series of 11 plans, 1946 - pencil on paper; 1 Drawing of revised mullions, 1947 - pencil on tissue
    Address: Payne Ave. & Santa Clara-Saratoga Rd.
    City: San Jose
  - Moore, Dr. La Rue; Medical Offices of Dr. Moore, 632 (Box Sc6)
    1 plan of medical offices, 1946 - pencil on paper
    Address: 515 Market Street, 3rd floor
  - Highway Elementary School, 633 (Box Sc6)
    5 drawings: plot plans, 1947, and portable steel barracks, 1946
    City: Mountain View, CA
  - West Bay Motors, 637 (Box Sc6)
    Plans, 1946
    Address: Main & Maple
  - Permanente Metals Corp.; Owen Lake Project, 638 (Box Sc6)
    Office and lab building, 1 drawing, 1946 - pencil on paper
    City: Owens Lake, CA
  - Carrere, Mrs. Marie, 643 (Box Sc6)
    2 drawings re repair and remodeling of fire damage, 1947
    Address: 79 Amador Avenue
  - Decoto Grammar School, 644 (Box Sc6)
    Series of 11 drawings, 1947
    City: Decoto, CA
  - Cahill, John, 645 (Box Sc6)
    Series of 7 plans, 1947 - pencil on paper
    Address: Whiskey Hill Road
    City: Woodside, CA
  - Bullis, R. S., 648 (Box Sc6)
    Proposed addition to residence, 3 drawings, 1947 - pencil on tissue
  - Washington Union High School, 649 (Box Sc6)
    Quonset hut, 1 plan, 1947 - pencil on paper
    City: Centerville, CA
  - E. T. Haas Co. Office Building, 658 (Box Sc3)
    4 plans, 1947 - pencil on paper
    Address: Harbor Boulevard
    City: Belmont, CA
  - Kimber, John E., 659 (Box Sc3)
    City: Niles, CA
  - Thompson Motor Parts, 663 (Box Sc3)
    Plan (1) for garage addition, 1948 - pencil on tissue
  - Jordan, R. N., 614
    Alteration of store building, 2 plans, 1945 - pencil on tissue
    Address: 431 Florence
  - Palo Alto Clinic, Ltd.; Clinic Addition, 1946-07-20; 627 (Box Sc6)
    18 plans: heating, electrical and plumbing, 1946
  - Walker, Kenneth, 653 (Box Sc3)
    3 plans for utility and dressing rooms, 1947; 1 plan remodel shop and dark room, 1970 (Clark, Stromquist & Sandstrom)
    Address: 189 Almendral Ave.
  - Clark, Dr. Esther, 369 (Box Sc4)
    12 plans, 1933
    Address: Old Trace Rd.
    City: Los Altos, CA
  - Morrill, G. F. (Box Sd10)
    Proposed residence for G. F. Morrill - 1 elevation, n.d.
  - Blichfeldt, H. F., 371 (Box Sc4)
    6 plans, 1933, 1 plan, 1934
    Address: 520 W. Crescent Drive
  - Bien, Joseph E., 372 (Box Sc4)
    Address: Manuella Rd.
  - Hamilton, Harold L., 379 (Box Sc4)
    15 preliminary plans, 1934
    Address: Loyola Dr.
  - Palo Alto High School; Palo Alto High School, 387 (Box Sc4)
    3 plans for 3 different projects, 1934
  - Palo Alto High School; Palo Alto High School, 388 (Box Sc4)
    Music and band building, 3 plans, 1934